let quiz = [
    {
        para: "The uttara kanda conjectures Rama's reign of Ayodhya, the birth of Lava and Kusha, the Ashvamedha yajna and last days of Rama. At the expiration of his term of exile, Rama returns to Ayodhya with Sita, Lakshmana, and Hanuman, where the coronation is performed. ",
        question: "His crown was made of Aluminium. Which element correctly represents Aluminium?",
        option: [
            "Fe",
            "Al",
            "Au",
            "He",

        ],
        answer: 2,
        
    },
    {
        para: "On being asked to prove his devotion to Rama, Hanuman tears his chest open and to everyone's surprise, there is an image of Rama and Sita inside his chest. Rama rules Ayodhya and the reign is called Ram-Rajya (a place where the common folk is happy, fulfilled, and satisfied).",

        question: "Let's heal hanuman. Which compound is used to heal wounds?",
        option: [
            "Hypochlorous acid",
            "Hydrochloric acid",
            "Nitric acid",
            "Sulphuric acid",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        para: "As time passes in the reign of Rama, spies start getting rumours that people are questioning Sita's purity as she stayed in the home of another man for almost a year without her husband. The common folk start gossiping about Sita and question Rama's decision to make her Queen.",

        question: "Anger is managed by these two chemicals released by our body",
        option: [
            "Endomorphin",
            "Dopamine",
            "Epinephrine and non-epinephrine",            
            "Metamorphin",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        para: "Rama is extremely distraught on hearing the news, but finally tells Lakshmana that the purity of the Queen of Ayodhya has to be above any gossip and rumour. Ram instructs him to take Sita to a forest outside Ayodhya and leave her there with a heavy heart. Lakshmana reluctantly drops Sita in a forest for another exile.",

        question:
            "What do plants inhale and exhale?",
        option: [
            "CO2 and O2",
            "N & H2O",
            "CuSO4 & O2",
            "H2SO4 & CO2",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        para: "Sita finds refuge in Sage Valmiki's ashram, where she gives birth to twin boys, Lava and Kusha. Meanwhile, Rama conducts an Ashwamedha yajna (A holy declaration of the authority of the king) and in absence of Sita places a golden statue of Sita. ",

        question:
            "Gold is inert in nature, but reacts easily with which of these?",
        option: [
            "Argon",
            "Halogens",
            "Krypton",
            "Xenon",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        para: "Lava and Kusha capture the horse (sign of the yajna) and defeat the whole army of Ayodhya which come to protect the horse. Later on, both the brothers defeat Lakshmana, Bharata, Shatrughan and other warriors and take Hanuman as prisoner. ",

        question: "Earlier, what were bows made of?",
        option: ["Iron", "Plastic", "Wood", "Gold"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        para: "Finally Rama himself arrives and defeats the two mighty brothers. Valmiki updates Sita about this development and advises both the brothers to go to Ayodhya and tell the story of Sita's sacrifice to the common folk. Both brothers arrive at Ayodhya but face many difficulties while convincing the people. ",

        question: "To build strength, what kind of food, should one eat?",
        option: [
            "food containing nutritions in ample amount",
            "Pure Veg",
            "Junk Food",
            "Non-Veg",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        para: "Then the most awaited moment arrives and Ram happily meets sita.",
        question:
            "When one is happy, endorphin is released in our body. Can you tell us how many endorphin structures are there?",
        option: ["alpha, beta, gamma, sigma", "6-alpha, 7-beta, 8-gamma", "alpha 22-beta", "4, alpha, beta, gamma, sigma"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        para: "On meeting Sita, Rama agrees to Sita's request to undergo an Agni Pariksha (test of fire) to prove her chastity, as he wants to get rid of the rumors surrounding her purity. ",
        question: "How can we stop a fire?",
        option: ["Using CO2", "Using O2", "Using He", "Using Petrol"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {   
        para: "When Sita plunges into the sacrificial fire, Agni, lord of fire raises Sita, unharmed, to the throne, attesting to her innocence.",
        question: "The crown had a ruby. What is the chemical formula for a ruby?",
        option: ["H2SO4", "CO2H2O", "Al2O3", "C9H9N3O2"],
        answer: 3,
    },
];